mvpweekly.com 2009-03-31

# AthletixNation Inc Social Media for Sports - Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY NOTICE

AthletixNation ("AXN") recognizes that our customers, visitors, users, and others who use www.axninc.com (the "Site") (collectively or individually "Users") value their privacy. This Privacy Notice provides important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Site. AXN provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Site. This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the AXN Terms of Use. Your use of the Site and any personal information you provide on the Site remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice.

### The Information We Collect

  * User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to AXN when choosing to participate in various activities on the Site such as uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters, other mailing lists, or signing up for a service or promotion that requires registration. For some services we may request credit card or other payment information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you give us with information from other AXN services or third parties in order to provide you with better services.
  * AXN Cookie: When you visit the Site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. AXN uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after your close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
  * Log File Information: When you use the Site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP)" address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * Clear GIFs Information: When you use the Site, we may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e. a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.
  * User Communications: When you send email or other communication to AXN we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 
  * Affiliated Sites: We offer some of our services in connection with other websites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to AXN in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.
  * Links: AXN may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising. For more information about links and redirected URLs, please see our FAQs.
  * Other Sites: This Privacy Policy applies to websites and services that are owned and operated by AXN. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

### The Way AXN Uses Information

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Site, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the site.
  * Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the Site and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Site changes or for customer service purposes). 
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

### When AXN Discloses Information

  * We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.
  * We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Site.
  * We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 
  * We also reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of AXN, our Users or others.

### Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the site, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the Site cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps, (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting your profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your op-in or opt-out choices using this contact form.

### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to those third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to op-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. You should consult the respective privacy policies of those third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to op-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, this is not a guarantee that such information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If we learn of a security system breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. The Web Site is not directed at children under 13 years of age, and the Company does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age online. 

### Special Note to International Users

The Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

### In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information your provided. Your continued use of the site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

### Date Last Modified

This Privacy Notice was last modified February 1, 2009.

### Contact Information

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice using this contact form.
